horoscopedays.com 2014-07-04

# Privacy Policy : Horoscope Days

This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information, which is given by You to Us , via the web site located at www.horoscopedays.com ("Site"). This Policy is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details. "You" shall mean you, the user of the Site. "We/Us" means HoroscopeDays. "Users" means the users of the Site collectively and/or individually as the context allows. 

### Data Collection

When using the Site You may encounter areas such as registration for chat forums, shopping or 'Add Video' where You may be asked to enter User Information. Such User Information will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected, for any other purposes specified at the collection point and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### How we may use your data

By entering Your User Information, You accept that we may retain Your User Information and that it may be held by Us or any third party company which processes it on Our behalf. We shall be entitled to use Your User Information for the following purposes:

  * market research, including statistical analysis of user behavior which we may disclose to third parties in depersonalized, aggregated form.
  * in order to enable Us to comply with any requirements imposed on us by law.
  * in order to send You periodic communications (this may include email), about features, products and services, events and special offers. Such communications from Us may include advertising for third party companies or organizations.

For your convenience you can withdraw consent by replying to the "unsubscribe" link in emails from us. Please also note that we do not disclose your personal information to third parties to enable them to send you direct marketing without your permission to do so.

### Cookies

You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of Cookies. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information that a web site can use to recognize repeat site visits and as an example, recall your name if this has been previously supplied. HoroscopeDays and selected business partners may use this to observe behavior and compile aggregate data in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on HoroscopeDays and other sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, click here.

### Security and Data Retention

Security is very important to Us. Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption technology is used for protection of information in transit for any sensitive transactions such as payments. Additional security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of Your User information. We will comply with all relevant Data Protection legislation in relation to the period for which We retain any information You disclose to us.

### Updates

You may notify Us of any updates, amendments and corrections to previously collected User Information by using the Feedback Form link in the Contact Us section of the site. We may change this privacy policy from time to time and you should check these regularly. Your use of the HoroscopeDays Site will be deemed an acceptance of the privacy policy existing at that time.

* * *
